本字幕由 PTT同志影视作品板 2013重新校稿
原字幕取自网路资源  仅供学习 禁用任何商业盈利行为
校稿：mohiwa
同志亦凡人 Queer As Folk S01E20
弗雷迪  你真他妈性感
Freddy, you are so damn hot.
像对镜头做爱一样　对  就是这样
Make love to that lens, make love to it, go on.
使劲干它  很好
Fuck it, that's it.
完美  简直完美
Beautiful. Beautiful.
真对我胃口
I love it!
《Babylon之王 》
-跟我来　　-好
- Come on.　- ll right.
《就在今晚 》
你能想像又过一年了吗
Can you believe it's been a whole year already?
从何时算起
Since what?
巴比伦之王大赛吧
Mmm. King of Babylon contest.
它每回都让人看起来很盛大
It always seems like such a big deal at the time,
等过一星期  都没人记得赢家是谁
and then like a week later, you can't even remember who won.
安琪儿·埃斯科巴
Angel Escobar.
身高156  体重175
5'10", 175...
腰围2尺1  阴茎长22CM
28" waist, 9" cock,
右腿内侧还有个普拉西多·多明戈
and a birthmark in the shape of Placido Domingo
形状的胎记
in his inner right thigh.
你可看得真专注
Wow, you were paying attention.
我该吃醋吗
Should I be jealous?
不必
No.
我吃不下甜点了
Think I'll skip dessert.
谁关心一堆类固醇过高的肌肉男
Ah, who cares about a bunch of steroid gym bunnies
穿着三角内裤在那翩翩起舞
dancing around in their jocks anyway?
考虑到去年你上了所有参赛者
Considering you've fucked off last year's contestants,
最关心的就是你吧
you?
天哪  谁会那麽做
God, who would do that?
谁不想和布莱恩上床啊
Who wouldn't fuck Brian?
不是这个
No.
我是说在那麽多人面前跳脱衣舞
I mean strip in front of all those people.
为了1000美金和巴哈马之旅
For 1,000 bucks and a trip to the Bahamas?
很多人会的
A lot of guys.
尤其当你嗑过药
Especially when you're on drugs,
拜托  你什麽都做得出来
please, you'll do anything.
呃…抱歉
Oops, sorry.
布雷克承认他有毒瘾
Blake acknowledges his addiction,
而且正在戒掉它
and he's working on it.
我在参加同志中心的戒瘾会
I've been going to meetings at the gay and lesbian centre.
哎呀  我们可不都有活儿在忙？
My, my, aren't we a busy little bee?
那麽  明天10点巴比伦门口见
So, um, we'll all meet in front of Babylon? 10:00 o'clock?
我不确定  我想大卫不会去的
I don't know. I don't think David's going to want to go
因为有点晚
'cause it's kind of late.
过了他要浸泡假牙的时间吗？
Does he already have his teeth in a glass by then?
我告诉你  他可每天早上6点就起床
I'll have you know he gets up at 6:00 o'clock every morning
然後晨跑五公里  而你还在睡大觉
and runs five miles, while you're still in bed.
床上是我锻炼心肺功能的地方
I feel that's where I get my best cardio workout.
如果我希望他去  他会去的
I'm sure he would go if I wanted him to.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
-是真的  -行啊
- It's true. - All right.
那就把他带来
Then make sure he's there.
没问题  我会
All right, I will.
行了吧
Okay. Okay.
-好极了  -最好是
- Great.    -Fine.
那麽  你们也来吗
So, you coming?
巴比伦不是完全禁毒的场所
Well, Babylon isn't exactly a drug-free environment.
布雷克是大孩子
You know, Blake's a big boy.
为何不让他自己决定
Why don't you let him decide?
我没问题的
I'm fine.
真的
Really.
算上我们
We're in.
万岁
Hooray!
不过  这开始像是「夫夫之夜」了
Only it's starting to feel perilously like a couples night,
看来我是唯一单身的
Seeing as I'm the only single boy left.
不好意思  那我是什麽
'scuse me, what the fuck do you think I am?
我们要去巴比伦是吗
Are we going to Babylon?
有什麽不对吗
What?
这些牛仔裤的洞太大而且太紧了
Those jeans are all torn and too tight.
啥
What?
我说这裤子又破又紧
I said those jeans are all worn and too tight.
之前怎麽没见你穿过
How come I haven't seen you in them before?
我只在没乾净衣服可穿时才穿
I only wear them when I don't have clean clothes.
以後再也不许你洗衣服了
Well, you must stop doing laundry immediately.
想出去玩吗
Do you feel like going out?
今晚有巴比伦之王比赛
Tonight's the king of Babylon contest.
迈克  我都一把年纪了  不适合那个
Oh, Michael, I'm too old for that shit.
不  你没那麽老
No, you're not.
我确实老了
Yes, I am.
听着  如果那些家伙看见
Huh. Look, if the guys saw
你穿上这条裤子会如此性感
how incredibly sexy you look in those jeans,
他们就不会
they'd prob- ably stop... Um...
-什麽　  -没什麽  别在意
-What?　-Nothing. Never mind.
-我什麽都不该说的　　　　-不　不
- I shouldn't have said anything. - No, no, no.
把话说完
Finish what you were going to say.
我打赌他们就不会再开成人尿布
I bet they'd stop making jokes about adult diapers,
假牙黏合剂
and denture cream and...
还有阴茎增大术的玩笑了
penile implants.
阴茎增大术？
Penile implants?
是你自己说的
Well, hey, you said it yourself,
你都一把年纪了  不适合那个
You're too old for this shit.
我就知道他们不会来
I knew they wouldn't come.
也许那老头需要迈克帮他按摩前列腺
Michael probably had to give the old man a prostate massage.
还有更糟的方式渡过周六晚上
There are worse ways to spend a Saturday night.
伙计们
Hey, boys.
抱歉我们迟到了
Sorry we're late, uh...
我得等大卫做完1000个仰卧起坐
Had to wait for David to finish his 1,000 sit-ups.
大卫  你看上去  棒极了
David, you... you look... great.
我是说  见到你真好
I mean, it's great to... see you.
好啦  够了没  进去吧
Okay, enough of this. Let's go inside,
里面有更多惹火的牛仔裤可看
where they have some more jeans.
你们先请
Yeah, why don't you go before us?
大家喝一杯吧
Hey, let's have a drink.
我请客
On me.
不了  我先去舞池转转
No, I think I'm going to go check out the dance floor.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
我也去
Same here.
还是谢谢啦
Thanks anyway.
我猜我不怎麽受欢迎
Guess I won't be winning any popularity contest tonight.
有问题的不是你
It's not your problem.
是他们  来吧
It's theirs. Come on.
-老兄                 -最近怎麽样
- He-ey, dude.     -How's it going?
最近都没看见你
Haven't seen you around.
我离开了一阵子
I've been away.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
要帮忙吗
Need a favour?
不  谢了
No thanks.
他是谁
Who's that?
谁都不是
Nobody.
我的药头
My dealer.
-以前的药头     -就知道我们不该来这儿
-Ex-dealer. 　　-I knew we shouldn't have come here.
没关系的
It's okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
听着  你得相信我  好吗
Look, you have to trust me, okay?
我相信
I do.
跳舞去
Let's dance.
先生们和先生们
Gentlemen and gentlemen,
有请今晚的主持人
welcome our hostess for the evening,
集高贵粗鲁於一身的  希巴
her royal rudeness, Sheba,
巴比伦皇后
Queen of Babylon.
得保证我高贵的双峰完好无缺
Gotta make sure the royal tits are intact.
行了  男孩们  闪吧
All right, boys. Go away.
自己一边玩儿去  回头见
Go play with yourselves. Ch-ciao.
欢迎来到第73届奥斯卡…
Welcome to the 73rd annual academy a...
噢  搞错了
Oops, wrong show.
欢迎来到巴比伦之王大赛
Welcome to the king of Babylon contest...
竞争是很激烈的    (Stiff亦指很硬)
Where the competition is stiff,
参赛者也是
and so are the contestants.
别急  小伙子们  你们还能报名
But don't fret, boys, you can still sign up
脱掉裤子  赢得奖金
to drop trou and win a thou.
好了  第一个参赛者 「消防员弗雷德」
All right, our first contestant is "four alarm Fred".
他将勾起你的火然後再扑灭它
He'll, uh, light your fire and put it out.
剃胸毛  隆胸肌
Shaved chest, pec implants.
还有类固醇
Steroids...
尽在多毛男人俱乐部
Hair club for men.
真是可悲  不是吗
Yeah, it's sad, isn't it?
这些老家伙们
All these older guys,
殊不知年华已逝
still partying way past their prime.
不知道该何时停下
They don't know when to stop.
所以我们来点实际的吧
So how about the real thing?
一小时後来找我
Check back with me in an hour.
什麽
What?
所以我只是候补吗
So now I'm a backup plan...
你没看到中意的才回头找我？
who you do when all else fails?
要跟你说多少次   我们不是情侣
How many times do I have to tell you? We're not a couple.
迈克和大卫是一对
Michael and David are a couple.
琳赛和茉蕾妮是一对
Lindsay and Melanie are a couple.
泰德和那个谁是一对
Ted and what's-his-name are a couple.
是啊  那我们是什麽  布莱恩
Yeah. So what are we, Brian?
我不知道你怎麽想的  不过
I don't know about you but...
我可是单身
I'm single.
商场向北走到尽头
...information desk at the north end of the mall.
你的儿子约翰在服务台等你
Your son John has been waiting for you.
嘿
Hey.
你好
Hello.
喜欢什麽消遣？
So, what are you into?
血拚一下
A little shopping.
晚餐  电影
Dinner, a movie.
朱莉娅·罗伯茨的新片
The new Julia Roberts.
我超级迷她
I just love her.
那你  想做点儿什麽吗
You, uh... want to do something?
不好意思
I'm sorry...
我不习惯在公共厕所做
But public restrooms aren't my scene.
那我们去别的地方怎麽样
Then how about we go some- place else?
老天  这儿的音乐也太吵了
God, the music's so loud in here,
连自己脑子里想什麽都听不见了
You can barely hear yourself think.
噢  现在好点了
Oh... that's better.
我都不知道自己干嘛一直来这儿玩
I don't know why I insisted on coming here.
每天都一个样
It's always the same.
对我有性趣的人  我看不上
The guys who are inter- ested in me, I'm not interested in them.
而我有性趣的人呢  看不上我
And the ones I'm interested in, well, aren't interested in me.
啊呀
Ah-h...
先生们和先生们
Gentlemen and gentlemen,
2号参赛者  警官奥来利
Contestant number two, officer O'reilly.
他可真是诱人犯罪啊  是吗？
He's very arresting, don't you think?
警官  我刚违规停车了
Officer, I just got a parking ticket.
叫我脱衣检查吧
Strip-search me!
这个比赛的问题在於它暴露了一条
The problem with this contest is that it exposes the single,
同志文化中最致命的缺点
most tragic flaw of gay culture.
它暴露的不只那个  大夫
It exposes a lot more than that, doc.
还有我们这种近乎病态的狂热
And that is our almost pathological obsession
渴望那些年轻  美丽
with youth, beauty
滑嫩  精壮的身体
and smooth, muscular bodies.
我知道  真是惭愧
I know, what a shame.
在我们摆脱这种幼稚
And until we break free of our stunted...
和肤浅的价值观之前
adolescence and our superficial values,
我们永远都成不了真正的男人
we'll always be boys, never men.
老天  就这样吗？
God, is that all?
我倒觉得大卫的话意味深长啊
I happen to find what David is saying to be profoundly insightful.
我觉得这些话真是满口胡扯
I find it to be profoundly full of shit.
这些自以为是的观点
An opinion put forth as truth
都出自那些伪君子  醋醰子
by a bunch of hypocritical, jealous,
爱内疚的  讨厌自已的
guilt-ridden, self-loathing
中年的  性无能的
middle-aged, sexually frustrated,
假聪明的娘炮
pseudo intellectual fags
然後还希望自己是异性恋
who wish they were straight.
那你干嘛不去报名
So why don't you sign up?
因为我不用穿着内裤跳舞吸引炮友上门
'Cause I don't need to dance around in my underwear to get laid.
或者…  你害怕和人竞争
Or maybe... you can't handle the competition.
我的老天  他要去报名了
Oh my god, he's going to sign up.
不  他才不会
No, he won't.
不可能
No way.
他真的去了
He is.
下一位参赛者是穆罕默德
Our next contestant is Mohammed.
他在健身中心教瑜伽
He's a master yoga instructor from ript gym.
他还能表演「自吹」哦
He can perform "auto fellatio".
这啥姿势啊
What the fuck's that?
是说在你车里口交吗
If that's giving a blow job in your car,
那我也算是大师级了
then I'm a master too.
该死  我身上这花开始凋谢了
Shit, I'm starting to wilt
明天在男孩玩具
and I've still got the "best pecs contest"
还要主持「最强胸肌大赛」
at Boytoy tomorrow.
这哭丧着脸是怎麽回事？  甜心儿
Mmm, what's with the long face, sweetheart?
没事
Nothing.
这男的
This guy.
不都因为男人吗？
Hmm. Ain't it always?
所以这个男的怎麽了？
So, what did this guy do?
他根本不把我当回事儿
He takes me for granted.
像你这样抢手的小帅哥
A walking wet dream like you
想要谁得不到
could  have anyone he wants.
我知道
I know.
那也是我生气的原因之一
That's the part I find so irritating.
也许他也应该发现这点
Maybe he needs to know it.
也许所有人都该发现这点
Maybe everybody needs to know it.
嘿  黛比  你电话
Hey, Deb. Telephone.
要是打来说我中奖   (一家专门抽奖的行销公司)
If it's publisher's clearing house,
告诉他们我去年就中奖了
tell them I won the sweepstakes last year.
是你弟弟
It's your brother.
噢
Oh!
维克  什麽事呀  亲爱的
Hey, Vic. What's up, honey?
千万别慌
Don't panic.
-我被逮捕了　　　 -什麽
- I've been arrested. 　-What?
-你先别慌呢　　 -好吧
- I said don't panic. - Alright!
别告诉任何人　  就连迈克也不能说
And don't tell anybody. Nobody. Not even Michael.
怎麽回事
What happened?
我在商场来着  当时我去厕所
I was at the mall, I went to pee.
那他们凭什麽抓你  因为没冲厕所吗
Well what are they charging you with? Not flushing?
不当猥亵露体罪
Indecent exposure.
不当…
Indecent...
你到底做了什麽？  对着别人甩老二吗？
What the hell'd you do, wag it at somebody?
我什麽都没做  老姐  我发誓
I didn't do anything, sis, I swear.
你能过来吗
Can you come down?
我在自由大道和格兰德道的第八区警局里
I'm on the zone 8 station on Liberty and Grand.
我这就过去  好吧
I'm leaving right now, all right?
-你冷静点 　　　 -能把我的药带来吗
-Just stay calm.　　- And could you bring my meds?
我一个小时之前就该吃药了
I should've taken them an hour ago.
好  别担心
Yeah, don't worry.
什麽都不用你操心
Don't worry about anything.
我无法解释
I can't explain it.
就好像
I-it's as though...
好像我们已经认识很久了
we've known each other all our lives.
没错
Exactly.
就好像  你一直在等我
As... as if you've been waiting for me...
而我也一直在等你
and I've been waiting for you.
同一个灵魂分成两半
Two halves of the same soul...
最後终於相遇
that have finally met.
太疯狂了
It's wild.
我知道  这对我自己来说过於主动了
Look, I... I know this is ridiculously forward of me...
我是说  我们几乎都不认识对方
I mean... I mean, we... Hardly know each other.
可你介意吗  就是...
But would you mind... that is,
这要求比较过分  如果我
very much... i-if I...
尽管来吧
Go right ahead.
还可以吗  我的亲爱的
Was that all right, my love?
就好像  圣诞节
It was like... Christmas...
新年  还有我的生日
and new year's and my birthday,
所有的惊喜都一起降临了
all rolled up into one.
没有美国独立纪念日吗
Not the fourth of july?
这个嘛   要留给你享受了
Well... I'm saving that for you.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
你去哪儿
Where you going?
厕所
Bathroom.
你觉得让他自己去好吗
Do you think it's a good idea to let him go alone?
你想让我帮他扶着吗？
Would you like me to hold it for him?
不是  我是说上次发生的那件事之後
No, I mean, after what happened last time.
这叫信任
It's called trust.
是啊　你可以确信他最後还是会被送去急诊
Yeah, you can trust he'll end up in the emergency room.
他不会的
Maybe he won't.
也许他会让你们都失望  然後好好的
Maybe he'll disappoint all of you and actually be all right.
当你还是个小屁孩的时候
When you were a boy,
你会去救那些翅膀受伤的小鸟吗
did you save the birds with the broken wings?
那你怎麽做  把他们撕碎吗
What did you do, tear them off?
同学们
Everybody...
我要给你们介绍一个非常特别的人
I want you to meet a very special someone.
-我叫布伦特    -布伦特
-I'm Brent.　　 -Brent!
-嗨  布伦特  -嗨
- Hi, Brent. - Hi.
你好啊  布伦特  欢迎
Hi... Brent. Hello, welcome.
艾美特觉得很重要的人  对我们来说也很重要
Anyone who's special to Emmett is special to us.
谁
Who?
艾美特
Emmett.
就是我  亲爱的
That's me, darling.
你俩认识多久了
How long have you two known each other?
这辈子的话  只是一小会
Well, I-in this life, only a... brief while.
不过  我相信前几辈子
But, uh... but I-I believe that in past lives,
我们就已经相遇很多次了
we've known each other many times before.
是不是
Uh, don't you?
这是我们有这麽多共同点的
Oh, it's the only explanation
唯一解释了
for how we could have so much in common.
简直难以置信
You can't believe it.
我们都喜欢布莱德·彼特
We both love Brad Pitt.
倩碧男性护肤品
Clinique for men.
特别是打折的时候
Especially when they're having a sale.
葱味薯片
Uh, green onion-flavoured potato chips.
还有我们最爱的歌
And our favourite song...
是「远处某地」
is "Somewhere out there".
这才叫不可思议
Now that's uncanny.
过来和我们喝几杯吧
Well, come and have a drink with us.
喂  怎麽了
Hey, what's up?
到底怎麽了
What's the problem?
艾美特才认识那个人15分钟
Emmett knows some guy for all of 15 minutes
他几乎就变成咱们的好兄弟了
and he's practically a frat brother.
而你几乎都不乐意搭理布雷克
Blake you can barely speak to.
也许是因为
Well, maybe that's because...
我不知道和他聊什麽
I don't know what to say.
「所以，你差点害死我的好朋友」
"So, you nearly killed my friend."
「我听说你在厕所昏倒了」
"Hey, I hear you passed out on the bathroom floor.
「想来点好东西吗」
You want to be buds?"
我一直觉得要是有人能给他个机会
You know, I figured if anyone could've given him a chance,
那个人就是你   迈克
it would've been you, Michael.
天哪  等一下
Hold on, Jesus!
来了
I'm coming.
怎麽了
What's the matter?
我一直给你们打电话打不通
I've been calling, But there's no answer.
我们晚上电话都关机
Oh, we turn the phone off at night.
怕把盖斯吵醒
It wakes Gus up.
真不好意思这麽晚过来打扰
I'm... I-I'm sorry to be coming by so late.
维克入狱了
Vic's in jail.
什麽
What?
他说他在商场厕所里
He said he was at the mall, he went to the men's room,
因为暴露罪被逮捕了  (妨碍风化)
and the next thing is they arrested him for indecent exposure.
暴露罪
Indecent exposure?
是  他发誓他什麽都没做
Yeah, he swears he didn't do anything.
他需要一个律师
But he needs a lawyer,
可是我不知道去哪
and I didn't know where to...
没事没事  我这就去换衣服
No, no, it's okay. I'm going to go get dressed.
要是他什麽都没做  干吗要抓他？
Well, if he didn't do anything, why did they arrest him?
他们就是看不惯同性恋
Oh, I-it's... harassment of gay people.
警察喜欢「钓鱼钓到甲鱼」
Cops just like playing "capture the fag".
你刚才什麽意思
What are you saying?
你是觉得维克真的做了什麽？
You think Vic did something?
我就是问一下
I was just asking...
告诉你  我了解我亲弟弟
Yeah well, I'm telling you, I know my own brother.
那罪名是瞎扯
And it's crap.
听我说  会没事的
Listen, it's going to be okay.
我现在去换衣服  咱们现在就走
I'm going to go get dressed, but we better get a move on.
我马上过来
I'll be right back.
你叫我一小时之後来找你
You said to check back with you in an hour.
还剩八分钟
I still have eight minutes left.
他屁股上有痘痘
He has zits on his ass,
小弟弟尺寸很悲剧
a tragic endowment,
而且刚从经历一场严重的淋病
and is just getting over a nasty case of gonorrhea.
如果我是你  我不会等太久的
Well, if I were you, I wouldn't wait too long.
到时候我可能已经也有其他计划了
By then I may have other plans.
你到底怎麽了
So, what's with you anyway?
没怎麽
Nothing.
你朋友是  什麽人啊
Who's your, uh... friend?
谁也不是
Nobody.
我看你俩挺亲密的啊
You look pretty tight to me.
你干吗不介绍我们认识
So how come you didn't introduce us?
他不会喜欢你的
He wouldn't like you.
也说不定
Maybe he would if I, uh...
要是我给他点猛料
Offered him a favour.
他不会对你的猛料感兴趣的
Yeah well, he's not interested in any of your "favours".
好东西
Great stuff.
好价钱
Great price.
我说了  我也没兴趣
And I told you, neither am I.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
我不过是
I'll be just a little looks like
在男厕外面转一转
loitering outside the men's room.
你来监视我的吗
Did you come to check up on me?
当然不是
'course not.
我刚遇见了这里最可爱的人
I just seem to meet the cutest guys here.
我跟你说了  我很好
'cause I told you, I'm fine.
我知道
I know.
来吧
Come on, let's, uh...
咱们去找其他人去
go find the others.
别去
Let's not.
我只想和你在一起
I'd rather just be with you.
绅士们都喜欢金发美女
Gentlemen prefer blondes,
而这个金发美女喜欢皮革猛男
and this blonde prefers gentlemen in leather.
让我们掌声欢迎德维恩
A big hand for Dwayne.
我一直梦想着住在一间小木屋里
I've always dreamt about living in a little cottage...
带後花园的那种
With a garden out back?
我可以在花园种满薰衣草和水仙花
W-where I can grow lavender and daffodils, and...
像我姑姑贝尔一样
wear a big sun bonnet,
戴着那种系头带的洋帽
like my aunt Belle, that ties under the chin.
我们可以用自己种的蔬菜
And we'll cook gourmet meals...
烹饪人间美味
seasoned with our very own herbs.
在飘雪的晚上　我可以在火炉前
And on snowy evenings, we'll curl up in front of the fire
抱在一起取暖品茗
with big mugs of hot tea.
夏天的时候
And... and in the summer,
我们慵懒地走在
we'll take long, lazy walks down a...
洒满夕阳余晖的乡间小路上
sun-dappled country lane.
人间天堂
It's heaven.
极乐世界
Bliss.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
别走开
Don't go away.
我就在这  等你
I'll be waiting... right here.
准备好和我耳鬓厮磨一整夜了吗
You had enough pulsating, grinding flesh for one evening?
随时随地
I'm ready to go whenever you are.
不  你还不能走
No, you can't leave yet.
你会错过我的重头戏的
You'll miss my big number.
就跟你真的会上台一样
Oh, right, like you'd really go through with it.
要是你现在走  就永远看不到了
Well, if you leave now, you'll never know.
德维恩
Dwayne!
要是德维恩成为了国王
If Dwayne becomes king,
其他人可要以他为标准啊
he'll be the ruler by whom all others are measured.
我可是亲自量过了他的尺寸
I ought to know, I measured him myself.
我们下一位参赛者是个喜欢吃嫩草
Right. Our next contestant likes younger men.
他的爱好是感觉高人一等
His favourite pastime is feeling superior.
他的特长是控制他人
His special skill is manipulating people.
就你了
Must be you.
让我们热烈欢迎匹兹堡最猛的理疗师
Let's put our hands together for Pittsburgh's hunkiest chiropractor,
大卫·卡麦伦医生
Dr. David Cameron!
你这混蛋
You asshole.
卡麦伦医生  寻找卡麦伦医生？
Dr. Cameron? Paging Dr. Cameron.
我以为你要自己上台呢
I thought you were signing up yourself.
我干嘛要那麽做
Now why would I want to do that,
有监於我发觉到人们对
when you know I find this obsession
青春、腹肌、和性爱的迷恋有多可怕
with youth and abs and sex so appalling?
你不必上去的
You don't have to go up there.
别担心  本来我也没想上去
Don't worry, I have no intention of it.
感谢老天
Thank god.
你不会想在你这把年纪
You wouldn't want to make a fool of yourself
穿着内裤扭来扭去的
dancing around in your underwear at your age.
别担心  医生  开个玩笑而已
Don't worry about it, doc, it was just a joke.
你觉得我做不来
Well, you think I can't do it?
在这把年纪
At my age?
寻找卡麦伦医生
Paging Dr. Cameron!
天哪
Mother of god!
卡麦伦医生
Dr. Cameron?
卡麦伦  卡麦伦
Dr. Cameron! Dr. Cameron!
大卫
David...
卡麦伦  卡麦伦
Dr. Cameron! dr. Cameron!
不是吧
He isn't.
是的
Yes, he is.
警官  不好意思  我们来看
Excuse me, sergeant? We're here to see...
维克多·格拉西
Victor Grassi.
格拉西
Grassi.
女士  不好意思
Oh, uh, sorry, ladies.
你们得等一下  他还在接受审讯
You have to come back later. He's still being processed.
我是他姐姐
But I'm his sister.
我是他的律师
And I'm Mr. Grassi's attorney.
你能告诉我他需要多少保释金吗
Could you just tell me how much his bail is set at?
五千块
5,000.
-什麽？　   -五千美元
-What? 　　-$5,000?
对一个初犯来讲是不是太高了
Isn't that high for a first offense?
这里写着他有过前科
Says here he's got a previous arrest.
-因为什麽  -携带违禁物品
- For what? - Possession of an illegal substance.
他是被拉下水的  那是十年前了
He was pulled over, it was 10 years ago.
杂物箱里有一卷大麻烟
There was a joint in the glove compartment.
那不是他的
It wasn't even his.
那他为什麽不反驳呢？
Then why didn't he say something?
因为即使在小时候
Because even when we were kids,
他也从没告发过我
he never squealed on me.
警官
Look, officer.
我弟弟病的很严重
my brother's very sick.
他得吃药
he's got to take his meds.
他有什麽问题
What's wrong with him?
他是HIV阳性
He's H.I.V positive.
哦  想也知道
Oh, figures.
你说什麽？
Excuse me?
要等这边的医生检查他之後
No drugs allowed in the holding cell
这些药才能带进拘留室
until the precinct doctors examine him.
但是这些是处方药
But these are prescription medications.
没了它们他活不了
His life depends on it.
要是他真病的这麽厉害
Well, if he's so sick,
他干吗要在公厕里晃来晃去
what was he doing hanging out in a public men's room?
撒尿啊
Taking a piss.
老天
Jesus.
走吧
Come on.
你太可爱了
You're so cute.
你的腹肌太帅了
You have great abs.
坚固的背部支撑和
Uh, well, they're... they're essential for, uh,
良好的姿势很重要
strong back support and good posture.
-打给我 　  -还有我
- Call me. 　-Yeah, me too.
随时奉陪
Anytime.
保证不会让你失望
I'll make it so worth your while.
有没有搞错？
Do you mind?
他已经名草有主了
He's already taken.
看你那得意劲儿
Well, I suppose you're pleased with yourself.
满脸春风的样子
Wipe that grin off your face.
把衬衫穿上！
Put your shirt on!
-迈克  　　　-别跟我罗嗦
- Michael... 　 -I don't want to hear another word about it.
-啊 　　  -给老娘过来
-A-ah!  　-Come here.
请注意  男孩们和男孩们
May I have your attention, boys and boys?
接下来的这位参赛者喜爱飞天小女警
The next contestant loves the powerpuff girls,
玛格丽特
Margaritas
还有一个不懂珍惜他的老男人
and older men who take him for granted.
有请…贾斯汀
Here's justin!
我  的  天  啊
Oh, my... god!
加油  宝贝
You go, baby!
等会
Wait.
你去哪儿？  我都开始担心了
Where were you? I was starting to worry.
对不起  有点事耽误了
Sorry. I got hung up.
没事
That's okay.
正好让我多想你一会
Gave me more time to miss you.
这样等你回来我就会更开心
And be even happier now that you're back.
-是古龙水吗  　　-嗯
-Is that cologne? 　-Huh?
应该是吧
I guess so.
我记得你没用古龙水
I don't recall your ever wearing cologne.
现在用了
I just started.
发生什麽事了吗
Is everything all right?
你好像有点心不在焉
You... you seem a little distant.
没什麽事
Everything's fine.
好吧
Okay.
我们说到哪儿了
Now, where were we?
对了  说到我们可爱的小屋
Um... oh, yes, in our cute little cottage.
不  等等
No, wait.
我不能欺骗你
I can't lie to you.
我们应该坦诚相待
We've meant too much to each other for that.
我刚遇到了一个人
I've met someone new.
刚遇到？
New?
我们在一起才1小时45分钟
We've only been together an hour and 45 minutes.
我也不想事情变成这样  我发誓
Look, I didn't mean for it to happen, I swear.
我从来没想过会伤害你
I never, never meant to hurt you.
脱！  小牛仔  脱！     (draw亦指拔枪出来)
Draw, cowboy! draw!
艾美特
Emmett!
等等
Wait.
你怎麽能这样对我
How could you do this to me?
对我们
To us?
-我们分享了那麽多　　　-别这样
- After all that we shared?　 - Please,
别把事情搞得更加复杂
don't make this harder than it has to be.
你说一生中从没和谁感觉这麽亲近过
You said that you never felt so close to anyone in your whole life.
你说我们是天生的一对
That... that we... we were two halves of the same soul.
世事多变
Things change.
凡人也多变
People change.
我还没变
I haven't changed.
我还爱你
I still love you.
激情会随着时间消逝
In time, passion dies.
你得接受它然後往前走
You have to accept it and move on.
好
Fine.
走吧  往前走
Go! move on.
没人拦着你
Who's stopping you?
我会记得你的
I'll remember you...
一直记得
always.
多久  到明天吗
Yeah, how long is that? Till tomorrow?
我给了你我一生中最好的时刻
I gave you the best minutes of my... life
你值夜班  是吧  警官
So you got the night shift, huh, sergeant?
我在餐厅也是上夜班
I did the same thing at the diner.
午夜到早上8点
Midnight to 8:00.
再加上8点到下午4点
In addition to 8:00 to 4:00.
连续16个小时
16 hours straight
就为了付我弟弟的医药费
To help pay for my brother's medical bills.
当你家里有人身体不好的时候
But you do that you know, when...
你不得不这样
someone in your family's sick.
你家里有人需要照顾吗
Is there anybody in your family who needs attention?
我妹妹是糖尿病患者
My sister's a diabetic.
她10岁的时候得的
She got it when she was about 10.
她现在还好吗？
Yeah, so how's she doing?
几年前她的腿截肢了
They cut her leg off a few years ago.
现在她正慢慢失明
Now she's losing her sight.
上帝保佑她
God bless her.
那我想你应该是
So, I imagine you'd swim the English channel
不辞辛苦地陪着她吧
to be there for her, huh?
事实上  我们不常见面
Actually, we don't see much of each other.
我们从没一起生活
We never got along.
不介意的话  我在工作呢
Now do you mind? I'm trying to work here.
就几片药而已
It's a few pills.
就该死的几片药而已
It's a few fucking pills.
没事
It's okay.
我们到哪儿去搞5千块
How the hell are we gonna get $5,000?
获胜者已经选出了
I believe we have a winner.
各位  准备屈膝迎接
Everybody, down on your knees,
我知道这是你们最爱的动作　(指跪下口交)
where I know you all want to be,
新一代巴比伦之王
for the new king of Babylon...
恭请我们的殿下
His royal highness...
贾斯汀
Justin!
不管那个不珍惜你的混蛋是谁
Whoever that asshole is who's been ignoring you,
他都不会再把你不当一回事了
he won't be taking you for granted any more.
谢谢你  谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
看到我表演了吗
Did you see me?
是  我看到了
Yeah, I saw you.
然後呢
Well?
我认为这个比赛有黑幕
I think that contest was rigged.
你认识他
You know him?
是的
Yeah.
他所有一切都是我教的
I taught him everything he knows.
除了跳舞
Except how to dance.
你叫什麽名字
What's your name?
我本该问他的   不过我想他肯定不知道
I'd ask him, only I'm sure he doesn't know.
肖恩
Shawn.
你真性感
You're hot.
我一直在注意你
I was watching you.
真的吗
You were?
你让我想整晚大干一场
You made me want to fuck all night.
-你想换个地方吗　　　　　-你带路
-You want to get out of here? 　-You lead.
我以为我们说好了
I thought we had plans.
你本来可以表现好一点
You couldn't do better.
我也说过我也可能有安排的
I told you I might have plans too.
他是怎麽回事
What's his problem?
他只不过是我的跟屁虫
He's just my stalker.
来个三人行也不错
I suppose we could have a three-way,
只不过  他看起来有点老
only, he's kinda old.
看起来我们也该走了
We're also kinda leaving.
他是不是有点逊
Is he doing some kinda lame?
不好意思
'scuse me,
是谁一个小时前还在说
But aren't you the person who said about an hour ago
他受够了这些无休止的
that they'd had enough of this pulsating,
躁动的肉体  说宁愿回家呆着
grinding flesh and wanted to go home?
-急什麽　　　　  -不是着急
-What's the rush?     -There's no rush.
我只是觉得你不太享受夜店
I just thought you didn't approve.
是你说的  对强壮光滑肉体的过分着迷
You know, all the misplaced emphasis on smooth, muscular bodies,
对年轻男体的痴迷  肤浅的价值观
the obsession with youth, and the shallow values.
也许我是有点太会批评了
Well, maybe I was being a little judgmental.
我觉得这叫伪君子
Try hypocritical.
-现在是谁太会批评了？            -实话实说而已
-Who's being judgmental now?　  -Just be honest.
别老是批评别人怎样
Don't put someone down for doing something
其实你一直都想做这些  就是没胆子做
you've always wished you could do, but didn't have the guts.
我回家了
I'm going home.
迈克
Michael.
-那是迈克 　　　   -所以呢
-There's Michael.  　-So?
所以...
Well so...
你整晚都没见到他了  难道你不想
You haven't seen him all night. Don't you want to...
我说过了  我想和你在一起
I already told you, I'd rather be with you.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
这样会不会有点
Is there some sort of...
什麽
What?
不妥  因为我
Problem? On account of me?
-当然不是        -要是那样的话
-Of course not.  - 'Cause if there is,
我不想成为你和你朋友间的绊脚石
I don't want to come between you and your friends.
你没有
You're not.
就算你有  也不要紧
Even if you were, it wouldn't matter.
听着
Look...
别这麽说
Don't say that.
我不想做什麽伤害你的事
I don't want to do anything to hurt you.
要是想到
If I ever thought
我成了你和你朋友间的绊脚石
I was going to come between you and your friends...
如果我的朋友对你有意见
If a friend of mine has a problem with you,
那只说明了他不是一个真正值得交的朋友
all it means is he was never really my friend to begin with.
迈克
Michael!
妈  茉蕾妮 你们在这儿干什麽
Ma, Melanie, what are you doing here?
布莱恩在哪儿
Where's Brian?
我想也许你能帮上忙
I-I was hoping maybe you could help.
我也想帮忙  黛比
Well, I would, Debbie,
但是我不可能让银行在周六晚上开门
but I can't really open a bank on a Saturday night.
信用卡行吗
Maybe credit cards?
不  ATM最多只能提款500块
No, the maximum withdrawal at an atm is $500.
我来处理吧　  他们收支票吗
I can cover it. Can they take a cheque?
除非是(银行)保付支票
Only if it's certified.
妈的
Shit!
这事儿还能再他妈的更烦人吗
I mean, could they make it any more fucking difficult?
我们必须要给个保释官打电话
Okay, you know what? We're going to have to call a bail bondsman.
打这个号码
If you call this number,
提这个名字
mention this guy's name,
他会付保证金的
He'll put up the bail for you.
这是怎麽回事
What was that all about?
我请迪诺帮忙的
I asked Dino for a favour.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢  你叫
Thank you, um...
布雷克
Blake.
布雷克  谢谢  我是黛比
Blake. Ah, thank you, I'm Debbie.
太谢谢你了
Oh! oh, oh, thank you!
你这朋友可真有办法
That's some friend you've got.
我也这麽想
I like to think so.
谢谢你
Oh, thank you!
你怎麽认识他的
Where'd you find him?
说来话长  黛比
It's a long story, Deb.
谢谢
Thanks.
别客气
No problem.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I've been...
之前很不客气
Shitty.
因为你关心泰德
It's because you care about Ted.
我也是
So do I.
我错过了什麽吗
Did I miss something?
-没有    -什麽
- No.      -What?
没事  没事
No. Nothing. Nothing.
都搞定了  走吧
Okay, we're all set. Let's go.
再次谢谢你
Thanks again!
天啊  老姐  我让你别和别人说
Jesus christ, sis, I told you not to tell anyone.
这没有什麽可不好意思的  维克叔叔
There's nothing to be ashamed of, Uncle Vic.
我们知道你是清白的
We know you're innocent.
我只是想回家  我们能回去了吗
I just want to go home. Can we please go home?
当然  我现在就送你回去
Yes, I'll take you home right now.
但是  你得先吃药
But first I want you to take your meds.
一晚上我都在想办法把药给你
I've been trying to get your meds to you all night.
没事的   柜台那个警官给我药了
It's all right, the desk sergeant gave me my pills.
走吧
Let's go.
我还是头一次见你这麽醋意大发
I don't think I've ever seen you so jealous.
-我没有吃醋　　　-看看谁在说谎
- I am not jealous. 　 -Oh, now who's being dishonest?
你会怎麽想
Well how would you feel
如果你男友被全城甲甲们色迷迷地盯着
if your boyfriend was being ogled by every fag in town?
他可常常被别人盯着看啊
It so happens he is.
哦  变成是我被人看了
Oh, I am, yeah.
经常有  只是你没注意过
Constantly. Only you never notice.
是  是我的问题  同志雷达常出错
Yeah. Oh, yeah. That's my problem, faulty gaydar.
我很幸运
Lucky for me.
现在你证明了即使到了你这个年纪
So now that you've proven to everyone how hot you are
也可以很性感   我想你现在
even at your age, I suppose you're going to...
会天天晚上出去玩了
be out partying every night.
不会每晚
Not every night.
不过我得承认  受人关注  知道自己
But it was nice to get the attention,
还很有魅力  感觉还是挺不错的
to know I'm still attractive. I must admit,
年轻男人那光滑紧实的身体  的确迷人
Hot young men with smooth, muscular bodies have a certain appeal.
但是还有其他东西
But there are other things.
工作  我儿子  还有你
Work. My son... and you.
那下次你没乾净衣服可穿   要换上这条裤子之前
So before you hang these jeans up until next laundry day,
给我跳段热舞怎麽样
How about doing a little dance for me?
这咖啡是给猪吃的
This coffee's for shit.
贾斯汀现在是新一代巴比伦之王
So Justin's the new king of Babylon.
长江後浪推前浪
So, the, uh, cub caught the lion's prey, hm.
就算你想享受你的成功
Even though you'd like to rest on your laurels,
保证的你的无上地位
secure in your position of power,
但现在他们越追越紧
now you know they're snapping at your heels.
而你需要加快速度奔跑
And you're going to have to run faster and faster...
你他妈能不能把那罐糖递给我
So why don't you pass the fucking sugar?
你应该为他骄傲
You should be proud of him.
虎父无犬子
Like father, like son.
那个是不是布伦特
Hey, isn't that Brent?
布伦特是谁
Who's brent?
艾美特的旧露水姻缘
Emmett's old flame.
另外一个肯定是新欢了
Must be with his new love.
你上哪去？
Where are you going?
很久没见了
Been a long time.
我很想你
I've thought of you...
常常
Often.
你看起来挺好的
You look good.
你也是
You too.
你有伴儿了吗
You seeing anyone?
没
Not really.
你呢
You?
我们刚刚认识
We just met.
那你今晚有空了
So you'll be free tonight.
没准
Probably.
-那你　　　　 -别
-Would you... 　-Don't!
我们回不去了
We can't go back.
我更倾向只是回忆
I prefer to remember...
我们以前的时光
the way we were.
向国王致敬
Hail to the king.
昨晚太爽了
What a night.
他怎麽样
So, how was he?
他的小屁屁超级紧
He had the greatest ass.
我带他到後面暗房  干了他一整晚
I brought him back, I fucked him all night.
我想小贾斯汀要酸痛一整个星期了
I think my dick's going to be sore for a week.
够了
That's enough.
实际上  我还想听
Actually, I'd like to hear more.
说清楚、讲明白
Speak slowly and enunciate.
呃，他很会口交
Uh, he gave great head.
他想我带着王冠干他
He wanted me to fuck him with my crown on.
有点变态
It's kind of kinky.
过了一会儿　  他开始想赖着不走了
After a while though, he got really clingy.
他问我他什麽时候还能见到我
He wanted to know when he could see me again...
你怎麽说的
So what'd you tell him?
我说你可以在梦里见我   (Brian曾在101对Justin说过)
I told him that he could see me in his dreams.
谁准备去「最猛腹肌大赛」？
Who's up for the Absolute abs contest?
3114ee634336439e8496cbe6e195de2e